

# PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication Leadership Time Management Self-Motivation Decision Making Team Work Self-awareness Punctual

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

C/C++ Python Front End Development Android App Development BackEnd Development

# CONTACT

P: +91 9205005951 E: aaruagarwal15@gmail.com W: aaruagarwal15.surge.sh

# **WORK SAMPLES**

Github https://github.com/aaruagarwal15 Profile - aaruagarwal15.surge.sh

# ARUSHI AGARWAL

### **ABOUT**

I am a person who loves to be positive in every aspect of life. I am very patient, responsible, punctual and hard-working student. I like to receive and deal with challenging tasks. I like to polish my skills, increase my knowledge and to share it. I always try to give my best in everything I do. I love to gain new experiences. I like to work with full honesty, integrity and dedication. I love to design websites and mobile applications.Outside of work, I like travelling and spending time with family and friends.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

ANDROID APP DEVELOPER INTERN
BSES Yamuna Power Limited| Jun 2019 - Jul 2019

WEB DEVELOPER INTERN
The Sparks Foundation | Mar-2019 - Apr 2019

TRAINING IN WEB DEVELOPMENT Coding Blocks | Jun 2018 - Jul 2018

## **EDUCATION**

INTEGRATED B.TECH M.TECH (CSE)

Jaypee Institute of Information Technology, Noida | 2016 - 2021 GPA 8.4

12TH (SCIENCE STREAM)

D.A.V. Public School, Kotdwara | 2015 - 2016

PER: 86.2%

### **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

Travelling ReadingListening Music Volunteer work Designing Websites